const STORE = {
  questions:[ 
  //Question 1
    {
    question: "Johnny Cash married his second wife in 1968. She was part of one of the most well known musical groups in country music history. What was her name?",
  answers: [
    "Dolly Parton",
    "June Carter",
    "May Carter",
    "Olivia Newton John"
  ],
  correctAnswer:
  "June Carter"
},

    //Question 2
    {
      question: "Singer George Jones went by this animal nickname?",
      answers: [
        "Possum",
        "Panda Bear",
        "Wombat",
        "Honey Badger"
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        "Possum"
    },

    //Question 3
    {
      question: "Which of these singers was NOT a member of The Highwaymen?",
      answers: [
        "Willie Nelson",
        "Kris Kristofferson",
        "Merle Haggard",
        "Waylon Jennings"
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        "Merle Haggard"
    },

    //Question 4
    {
      question: "This singer was supposed to be on the same plane that crashed and killed Buddy Holly, but he gave his seat up to the Big Bopper--who also died in the crash.",
      answers: [
        "George Jones",
        "Waylon Jennings",
        "Porter Wagoner",
        "Johnny Cash"
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        "Waylon Jennings"
    },

    //Question 5
    {
      question: "What is Johnny Paycheck's real name?",
      answers: [
        "Henry Deutschendorf Jr.",
        "Hiram Williams",
        "Donald Lytle",
        "Ira Loudermilk"
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        "Donald Lytle"
    },

    //Question 6
    {
      question: "Who wrote Johnny Paycheck's 1977 number one hit song“Take This Job and Shove It?",
      answers: [
        "Tom T. Hall",
        "David Allan Coe",
        "Guy Clark",
        "Swamp Dogg"
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        "David Allan Coe"
    },

    //Question 7
    {
      question: "At which prison did Johnny Cash NOT record a live album?",
      answers: [
        "Tennessee State Prison",
        "Folsom State Prison,
        "San Quentin State Prison",
        "Leavenworth Federal Penitentiary"
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        "Tennessee State Prison"
    },

    //Question 8
    {
      question: "After his wife hid all of his car keys, what mode of transportation did George Jones famously use to get to the liquor store 8 miles away?",
      answers: [
        "A horse",
        "A jet ski",
        "A riding lawnmower",
        "Roller skates"
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        "A riding lawnmower"
    },

    //Question 9
    {
      question: "Singer and songwriter Gram Parsons overdosed on morphine in 1973 during a trip to visit which national park?",
      answers: [
        "Big Bear",
        "Grand Canyon",
        "Joshua Tree",
        "White Sands"
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        "Joshua Tree"
    },

    //Question 10
    {
      question: "In 1975, Hank Williams Jr. almost died accidentally while doing what activity?",
      answers: [
        "Motorcycle stunts",
        "Rock climbing",
        "Fleeing the police to avoid a DUI",
        "Shaving"
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        "Rock climbing"
    },

    //Question 11
    {
      question: "In 1981 Johnny Cash was hospitalized after being attacked by an animal from his own personal zoo. What kind of animal was it?",
      answers: [
        "Alligator",
        "Ostrich",
        "Chimpanzee",
        "Wolverine"
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        "Ostrich"
    },

    //Question 12
    {
      question: "Name the first track off of Willie Nelson's 1975 album“Red Headed Stranger.,
      answers: [
        "Red Headed Stranger",
        "Blue Eyes Cryin' in the Rain",
        "Time of the Preacher",
        "Whiskey River"
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        "Time of the Preacher"
    },